Finding Aid for the Renée Levine Packer Papers, 1963-circa 2015
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Book, interview, and research files for This Life of Sounds 1963-2011, II.; Folder 18-380
  - Subject files, circa 1999-2010, II.D; Folder 99-267
    - Pablo, Luis de, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 214)
    - Paik, Nam June, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 215)
    - Perlis, Vivian, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 216)
    - Pierce-Arrow Motor Car Company - Buffalo plant, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 217)
      Home of DOMUS Theater Company in 1970s.
    - Piene, Otto, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 218)
    - Poons, Larry, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 219)
    - Powell, Mel, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 220)
    - Rich, Alan, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 221)
    - Riley, Terry, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 222)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 223)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 224)
    - Rockefeller Archive Center - Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 225)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Annual report, 1964, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 226)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Lukas Foss consultancy, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 227)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Original proposal draft for Center of the Creative and Performing Arts, 1963, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 228)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Original grant for Center of the Creative and Performing Arts, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 229)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Deliberations, 1963-1968, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 230)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Correspondence, 1964-1968, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 231)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Supplementary correspondence and reports, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 232)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Grant, supplementary request, 1965, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 233)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Grant, extension request, 1966, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 234)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Interdisciplinary grants, 1970, 1978, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 235)
    - Rockefeller Foundation: Technical grants and proposals, 1977, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 236)
    - Rockwell, John, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 237)
    - Ross, Alex, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 238)
    - Russell, John, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 239)
    - Rzewski, Frederic, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 240)
    - Sapp, Allen, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 241)
    - Satie, Erik: Vexations, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 242)
    - Siemering, William, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 243)
    - Slatkin, Leonard, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 244)
    - Smit, Leo, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 245)
    - Source magazine, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 246)
    - Spitzer, John, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 247)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo: History, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 248)
      Articles by Warren Bennis and Barbara Probst Solomon.
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 249)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo. University Archives, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 250)
    - Strauss, Madeleine, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 251)
    - Takemitsu, Toru, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 252)
    - Tilbury, John, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 253)
    - Tilson Thomas, Michael, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 254)
    - Thomson, William, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 255)
    - Tudor, David, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 256)
    - Vigeland, Nils, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 257)
    - Weinstein, Harvey and Corky, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 258)
    - Williams, Jan, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 259)
    - Winter, Monica (Polowy), 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 260)
    - WNED-TV, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 261)
    - Wolpe, Stefan, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 262)
    - Woodstock Festival, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 263)
    - Xenakis, Iannis, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 264)
    - Yadzinski, Edward, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 265)
    - Yates, Peter, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 266)
    - Young, La Monte, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 267)
  - Supplementary University at Buffalo Music Library Catalogs and University at Buffalo publications about student unrest, 1970-1998, II.E; Folder 268-306
    Contains catalogs produced by the University at Buffalo Music Library for concerts other than those produced by the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts. Also contains University at Buffalo publications, chiefly from 1970-1973, concerning campus unrest and protests.
    - Buffalo Musicians, 1998, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 268)
    - June in Buffalo, A Catalogue, 1975-1980, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 269)
    - North American New Music Festival program, 1993, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 270)
    - Slee Lecture Recitals, A Catalogue, 1957-1976, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 271)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo: Student unrest - Student publications, 1970-1973, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 272-306)
      Includes issues of Spectrum, Ethos, Reporter, Undercurrent, and Dimension.
  - Interview recordings, circa 1999-2001, II.F; Item 307-354
    Cassette and microcassette recordings of interviews.
    Alphabetically arranged by interviewee surname.
    - Amacher, Maryanne, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 307)
    - Bannon, Anthony, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 308)
    - Bergamo, John, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 309)
    - Berlow, Sheldon, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 310)
    - Brigham-Dimiziani, Sylvia, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 311)
    - Brown, Earle, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 312)
    - Buck, Robert, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 313)
    - Crumb, George, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 314)
    - Felder, David, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 315)
    - Foss Lukas, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 316)
    - Fox, Stuart, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 317)
    - Fuller, David, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 318)
    - Harriott, Esther, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 319)
    - Hassell, Jon, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 320)
    - Haupt, Charles, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 321)
    - Jackson, Bruce, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 322)
    - Kotík, Charlotta, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 323)
    - Kotík, Petr, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 324)
    - Kubera, Joseph, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 325)
    - La Barbara, Joan, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 326)
    - Lawson, Christyne, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 327)
    - Levine, George, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 328)
    - Levine-Packer, Renée, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 329)
    - Martin, Robert, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 330)
    - Mischel, Howard, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 331)
    - Plantamura, Carol, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 332)
    - Rosenboom, David, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 333)
    - Sahl, Michael, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 334)
    - Schneider, June, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 335)
    - Shostac, David, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 336)
    - Siemering, William, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 337)
    - Vasulka, Steina, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 338)
    - Vasulka, Woody, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 339)
    - Vigeland, Nils, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 340)
    - Warren, Gwendolin Sims, 2 audio cassettes (Box 13, Item 341-342)
    - Wernick, Richard, 2 audio cassettes (Box 13, Item 343-344)
    - Williams, Diane, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 345)
      With Alyssa Rabach Anthone on Side 2.
    - Williams, Jan, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 346)
    - Winter, Monica Polowy, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 347)
    - Yadzinski, Edward, 1 audio cassette (Box 13, Item 348)
    - Globokar, Vinko, 1 microcassette (Box 13, Item 349)
    - Marcus, Bunita, 1 microcassette (Box 13, Item 350)
    - Packer, Randall, 1 microcassette (Box 13, Item 351)
    - Stiller, Andrew, 2 microcassettes (Box 13, Item 352-353)
    - Verberne, Marijke, 1 microcassette (Box 13, Item 354)
  - Electronic files for book and interview transcripts, circa 1999-2010, II.G; Item 355-380
    Floppy 3.5 inch diskettes chiefly containing Microsoft Word files used for storing versions of the thesis files as well as drafts of the interview transcriptions. Item titles transcribed from diskette labels.
    - MLA text Section 1, Thesis text, 2001-01-15, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 355)
    - MLA-I, 2001-02-15, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 356)
    - MLA thesis p. 1-5, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 357)
    - Final thesis, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 358)
    - CA manuscript, 2004-10-04, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 359)
    - Evenings for New Music, 2004-10-20, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 360)
    - Manuscript and intro saved, 2005-05-06, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 361)
    - Maryanne Amacher, 2003-01-02, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 362)
    - Interviews with Alyssa Rabach Anthone, Ed Yadzinsky, Diane Williams, Charles Haupt, George Levine, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 363)
    - Anthony Bannon, 2002-03-20, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 364)
    - Stuart Fox, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 365)
    - Stuart Fox - edited; Esther Harriott, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 366)
    - David Fuller, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 367)
    - Joe Kubera, June Schneider, Earle Brown, David Shostac, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 368)
    - Christyne Lawson, Sheldon Berlow, David Felder, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 369)
    - Interview with Renée Levine-Packer by John Spitzer, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 370)
    - Bob Martin, 2000-11-17, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 371)
    - Siemering, Buck, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 372)
    - Gwen Sims, 2002-10-18, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 373)
    - Interviews with Richard Wernick, George Crumb, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 374)
    - Diane Williams, Alyssa Rabach, Ed Yadzinsky, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 375)
    - Jan Williams, Carol Plantamura, Fox, Kotik, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 376)
    - Backup of all CA files - interviews as of 1/5/01 (up to J. W.) #1, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 377)
    - Backup of CA interviews as of 1/5/01 #2, 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 378)
    - CA interviews (backup), 1 3.5 inch diskette (Box 14, Item 379)
    - This life of sounds, Figures 1.2, 1.3, 1 CD-ROM (Box 14, Item 380)
- Production files for Robert Longo's Killing Angels, 1983-1989, III.; Folder 381-392
  Documentation of Renée Levine Packer's rôle as producer of the 1987 production of Robert Longo's Killing Angels at Buffalo State College.
  - Proposal to Art Matters, Inc. for the creation and performance of Killing Angels, 1987, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 381)
  - Agreement with Buffalo State College, 1987, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 382)
  - Presentation on Killing Angels, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 383)
  - Killing Angels - List of sections and durations, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 384)
  - Killing Angels -Stage design drawings, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 385)
  - Killing Angels -Stage design model illustrations, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 386)
  - Killing Angels - Cast list, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 387)
  - Killing Angels - Programs, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 388)
  - Killing Angels - Clippings, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 389)
  - Killing Angels - Publicity, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 390)
  - Sixteen 35 mm color slides of Longo works - Marble fog, Ornamental love, Tongue to the heart, Heaven, Samurai overdrive, Now is a creature, 1 sleeve (Box 15, Folder 391)
  - Program for UCLA performance of Longo's Dream Jumbo, 1989-10-06, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 392)
- Production files for Steve Reich and Beryl Korot's The Cave, 1993-2006, IV.; Folder 393-398
  Documentation of Renée Levine Packer's rôle as producer of the 1993 productions of Steve Reich and Beryl Korot's The Cave at the Brooklyn Academy of Music, Wiener Festwochen, and the Paris Autumn Festival.
  - Clippings about Steve Reich and Beryl Korot's The Cave, 1989-2006, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 393)
    1989-06-03: Washington Post. Harrington, Richard: The evolving Steve Reich: from the composer, sound structures, minimal and maximal -- 1989-07-09: Los Angeles Times. Schrag, Carl: Searching for Abraham and Ibrahim -- 1991-02-06: Times (London). Gray, Louise: Identity parade in an ancient cave: minimalist composer Steve Reich looks to his roots for inspiration -- 1993? Baltimore Jewish Times. Greenberg, Melinda: Cave explorations -- 1993-05-19: Times (London). Griffiths, Paul: Voices in search of harmony: a Steve Reich premiere in Vienna -- 1993-05--1993-10. Compilation from multiple sources -- 1993-05-29: International Herald Tribune. Rockwell, John: Vienna Festival: Much more than waltzes -- 1993-06: Magazine of The Netherlands Holland Festival -- 1993-06-11: Guardian. Sweeting, Adam: Tiers of despair -- 1993-06-12: Financial Times (London). Clements, Andrew: A cave full of treasures -- 1993-06-14: New York Times. Kozinn, Allan: Next Wave Festival to open with premiere -- 1993-06-14: Time Magazine. Walsh, Michael: Words sliced and diced -- 1993-08-20: Guardian. Bowen, Merion: The Reich stuff: Steve Reich's ground-breaking The Cave at the RFH -- 1993-08-21: Times (London). Brunskill, Ian: Sounds with vision -- 1993-08-29: Observer (London). Porter, Andrew: Music -- 1993-09-12: New York Times Magazine. Woodward, Richard B.: Songs of a wired cave -- 1993-10: Opera News. Schwarz, K. Robert: Witnesses -- 1993-10-10: New York Times. Schwarz, K. Robert: The Cave walks, but doesn't quack, like an opera -- 1993-10-12: USA Today. Stearns, David Patrick: Politics resonate in The Cave -- 1993-10-15: New York Newsday. Stuart, Jan: Seeds of Arab-Israeli conflict in The Cave -- 1993-10-21: Le Nouvel Observateur. Anquetil, Gilles: Les chants d'Abraham -- 1993-10-28: Le Soir. Debrocq, Michel: Steve Reich et Beryl Korot donnent naissance au videopera -- 1993-10-29: Le Monde. Rey, Anne: Proposition d'operas -- 1993-11-02: Village Voice. Gann, Kyle: Inside-out opera -- 1995-12-15: Guardian. Clements, Andrew: In search of Abraham -- 1997-08-24: New York Times. Taruskin, Richard: A sturdy musical bridge to the 21st century -- 1999-07-17: New York Times. Oestreich, James W.: Reich's amalgam of speech and melody -- 2006-11-04: New York Times. Tommasini, Anthony: Abraham, Sarah and video (of course)
  - Program and notes for Steve Reich and Beryl Korot's The Cave, 1993, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 394)
    Including Jonathan Cott interview with Steve Reich and Beryl Korot.
  - Wiener Festwochen performance of The Cave - program and clippings, 1993, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 395)
  - Lincoln Center Festival program for performance of The Cave, 1999, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 396)
  - Correspondence between Renée Levine-Packer and Steve Reich, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 397)
  - Concert programs for other Reich works: The Desert (1986), Three Tales (2002), and Hindenburg (1998), 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 398)
- John Cage files, 1981-2007, V.; Folder 399-410
  John Cage materials not related to the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts. The contents include programs, clippings, materials for Cage programs presented at Cal Arts and the Maryland Institute, College of Art. The score and accompanying film and sound recordings for Cage's Lecture on the weather are also included.
  - Clippings and programs, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 399)
  - Alphabet lecture presented at Cal Arts, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 400)
  - Diary: Inter Arts: given as a talk before the National Council on the Arts, 1983-02-04, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 401)
  - For Renee W. Levine, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 402)
    Acrostic by John Cage for Renée Levine-Packer.
  - Peter Gena writings on John Cage, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 403)
  - Laura Kuhn letter regarding John Cage, 1986-06-30, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 404)
  - Maryland Institute, College of Art: documents regarding presentation of John Cage's Lecture on the weather, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 405)
  - Score of John Cage's Lecture on the weather, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 406)
    Published by C. F. Peters.
  - Accompanying cassettes of sound source for Lecture on the weather, 3 audio cassettes (Box 16, Item 407-409)
  - Accompanying film for Lecture on the weather, 1 film reel (Box 16, Item 410)
- Personal correspondence, 1965-2007, VI.; Folder 411-440
  Contains personal correspondence chiefly unrelated to the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts research. Some of the original correspondence was sold to an antiquarian dealer and is now represented in the collection by photocopies. The correspondence with Betty Freeman is followed by some ancillary material because she is not represented elsewhere in the collection.
  Alphabetically arranged by correspondent surname.
  - Anthone, Alyssa Rabach, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 411)
  - Brown, Earle, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 412)
  - Bussotti, Sylvano, 1965, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 413)
    Consists of photocopy of artwork created by Bussotti for Levine-Packer.
  - Cage, John, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 414)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 415)
  - Foss, Lukas, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 416)
  - Freeman, Betty - Correspondence, 1983-2007, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 417)
    Contains 19 pieces of correspondence.
  - Freeman, Betty - Flyers and programs, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 418)
  - Freeman, Betty - Clippings, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 419)
  - Freeman, Betty - Correspondence from Renée Levine-Packer to Betty Freeman and her daughter, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 420)
  - Goodman, Benny, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 421)
  - Haupt, Charles and Irene, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 422)
  - Jolas, Betsy, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 423)
  - Kolb, Barbara, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 424)
  - Kondo, Jo, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 425)
  - Kotík, Petr, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 426)
  - Kraber, Karl, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 427)
  - Kubota, Shigeko, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 428)
  - Neuhaus, Max, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 429)
  - Pablo, Luis de, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 430)
  - Plantamura, Carol, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 431)
  - Powell, Mel, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 432)
  - Rands, Bernard, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 433)
  - Roqué Alsina, Carlos, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Schneider, Mischa, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 435)
  - Sharits, Paul, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 436)
  - Smit, Leo, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 437)
  - Sollins, Susan (Brown), 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 438)
  - Takemitsu, Toru, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 439)
  - Xenakis, Iannis, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 440)
- Books with inscriptions, 1975-2007, VII.; Item 441-462
  Date range represents publication dates of the texts, not when they were inscribed or received. The one unpublished text is the beginning of a memoir by violoncellist Mischa Schneider.
  Alphabetically arranged by author surname.
  - Blum, Eberhard: Anthology, vol. 3 1968-98, 2000, 1 book (Box 17, Item 441)
    Publisher: Heenemann
    Inscribed to Renée and Arnie.
    Two CD recordings issued in book jacket format.
  - Blum, Eberhard: Eberhard Blum: Recordings on CD, 1990-1996, 1997, 1 book (Box 17, Item 442)
    Publisher: H. Heenemann
    Inscribed to Renée and Arnold.
  - Blum, Eberhard: Eberhard Blum: Visual work, 1980-98, 1998, 1 book (Box 17, Item 443)
  - Blum, Eberhard: Eberhard Blum: Visual work, 1992-2005, 2006, 1 book (Box 17, Item 444)
    Publisher: Ruksaldruck
  - Cage, John: For the birds: John Cage in conversation with Daniel Charles, 1981, 1 book (Box 18, Item 445)
    Publisher: Marion Boyars
    Inscribed to Renée Levine.
  - Davis, W. Bowdoin: Duchamp: domestic patterns, covers, and threads, 2002, 1 book (Box 18, Item 446)
    Publisher: Midmarch Arts Press
    Inscribed to Renée Levine-Packer.
  - Freeman, Betty: Music people: Photographs, 2003, 1 book (Box 18, Item 447)
    Publisher: Palladion Book for Carnegie Hall
  - Freeman, Betty: Music people and others, 1987, 1 book (Box 18, Item 448)
    Publisher: Mazzotta
  - Garland, Peter: Americas: Essays on American music and culture 1973-80, 1982, 1 book (Box 18, Item 449)
    Publisher: Soundings Press
  - Goldstein, Malcolm: Sounding the full circle: concerning music improvisations and other related matters, 1988, 1 book (Box 18, Item 450)
    Publisher: M. Goldstein
  - Khlebnikov, Velimir: King of time: Selected writings of the Russian futurian, 1985, 1 book (Box 18, Item 451)
    Publisher: Harvard University Press
    Inscribed to Renée Levine-Packer by the translator, Paul Schmidt.
  - Lehmann, Ann Holyoke: Of a piece: second part of an autobiographical methodology, 2005, 1 book (Box 19, Item 452)
    Publisher: A. Lehmann
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Center for Advanced Visual Studies: Arttransition, 1975, 1 book (Box 19, Item 453)
    Publisher: MIT
    With content regarding Gerald O'Grady and Maryanne Amacher.
  - Neuhaus, Max: Sound installation, 1983, 1 book (Box 19, Item 454)
    Publisher: Kunsthalle Basel
  - Nordheim, Arne: My longing is not my own, 2001, 1 book (Box 19, Item 455)
    Publisher: Royal Norwegian Ministry of Foreign Affairs
    Card inserted with inscription to Renée Levine-Packer.
    Includes CD recording of Nordheim's music.
  - Piatigorsky, Jacqueline: Jump in the waves, 1988, 1 book (Box 19, Item 456)
    Publisher: St. Martin's Press
    Inscribed to Eva Feuermann Lehnson by Jacqueline Piatigorsky.
  - Reich, Steve: Writings on music, 1965-2000, 2002, 1 book (Box 19, Item 457)
    Publisher: Oxford University Press
  - Ross, Alex: Rest is noise: listening to the twentieth century, 2007, 1 book (Box 20, Item 458)
    Publisher: Farrar, Straus and Giroux
  - Music for Mischa: a fall season of Sunday afternoon concerts of chamber music, 1988, 1988, 1 book (Box 20, Item 459)
    Inscribed to Renée Levine-Packer by June Schneider.
  - Schneider, Mischa: Beg. of the book I stopped writing, undated, 1 book (Box 20, Item 460)
    Card inserted with inscription to Renée Levine-Packer by June Schneider.
    Copy of typescript through page 39.
  - Schwartz, Elliott: Contemporary composers on contemporary music, 1967, 1 book (Box 20, Item 461)
    Publisher: Holt, Rinehart and Winston
    Co-edited by Barney Childs.
  - Smith, Patrick J.: Year at the Met, 1983, 1 book (Box 20, Item 462)
    Publisher: Alfred A. Knopf
- Programs and journal issues, 1980-2013, VIII.; Folder 463-473
  Programs and journals collected chiefly unrelated to work projects.
  - Programs, 1984-1985, 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 463)
  - Programs, 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 464)
  - Programs, 1990-1996, 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 465)
  - Programs, 2000-2009, 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 466)
  - Programs, 2013, 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 467)
  - Programs, undated, 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 468)
  - California Institute of the Arts programs and publications, 1980-1986, 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 469)
  - Dance and art clippings, 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 470)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art. Art and dance: Images of the modern dialogue, 1890-1980, 1982, 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 471)
  - Performing Arts Journal, 26/27, 1985, 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 472)
  - Museum International no. 189, v. 48 no. 1, 1996, 1 folder (Box 21, Folder 473)
- Photographs, circa 1964-1992, IX.; Item 474-539
  Photographs chiefly related to the personnel of the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts, including Renée Levine Packer, Lukas Foss, Carol Plantamura, John Cage, Jan Williams, and Julius Eastman. Photographers in the collection include Betty Freeman, Jim Tuttle, and Mickey Osterreicher.
  - Renée Levine portrait, circa 1964, 1 black and white photograph (Box 22, Item 474)
    Unidentified photographer
  - Lukas Foss, Renée Levine, and Henri Pousseur, 1967, 1 black and white photograph (Box 22, Item 475)
    Tuttle, Jim
  - Renée Levine and Lejaren Hiller, 1971, 1 black and white photograph (Box 22, Item 476)
  - Renée Levine and Jan Williams, 1970, 1 black and white photograph (Box 22, Item 477)
    Greenberg-May Productions
  - Renée Levine and Jan Williams, 1974, 1 black and white photograph (Box 22, Item 478)
    Osterreicher, Mickey
  - Renée Levine and Morton Feldman, 1977, 1 black and white photograph (Box 22, Item 479)